jobvine.co.za 2010-06-17

# South Africa jobs » Privacy Polices

##  Privacy Policy for [www.JobVine.co.za](http://www.jobvine.co.za/)

At JobVine we are dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us. 

This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms and Conditions, provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you. 

We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

The term ‘JobVine’, ‘us’, ‘our’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of this website whose registered office is in Cape Town, South Africa. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.

** 1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

1.1 In operating our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

(a)    Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.

(b)    Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you register as a **job seeker** or **recruiter** (see paragraphs 1.2 and 1.3). 

(c)    Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

1.2 If you are a **job seeker** , you must complete the registration form. During registration you are required to provide is with some personal information.

1.3 If you are a **recruiter** , you are required to provide us with your company, as well as personal information.

** 2\. USE OF COOKIES**

2.1   On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers. 

2.2   Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. 

2.3   Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file.  Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you. 

2.4   All computers have the ability to decline cookies.  This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.

2.5   Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  

** 3\. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

3.1 The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you.  In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

(a)    To meet our contractual commitments to you.

(b)    To inform you of any notices, including changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes that may affect our service.

(c)    To alert you when similar jobs are posted to the ones you have applied for. 

(d)    To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. 

(e)    If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you. 

(f)     Further, we may use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, so that you can be provided with information about unrelated goods and services which we consider may be of interest to you.  We or they may contact you about these goods and services by any of the methods that you consented at the time your information was collected.

(g)    If you are a new customer, we will only contact you or allow third parties to contact you when you have provided consent and only by those means you provided consent for. 

(h)    If you do not want us to use your data for our or third parties you will have the opportunity to withhold your consent to this when you provide your details to us on the form on which we collect your data.

(i)     Please be advised that we do not reveal personally identifiable information to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors. 

(j)     To allow Jobvine approved recruiters to view and access your personal details (including your Curriculum Vitae) in order to find the best candidate to fill a vacancy. Approved JobVine recruiters are recruiters who have registered with and advertise jobs on the website.

(k)     Jobvine is not responsible for any improper use of personal information by recruiters.

** 4\. DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION __**

4.1 In addition to paragraph 4, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company and its other subsidiaries (if any).

4.2 We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

(a)   Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.

(b)   Where we are legally required to disclose your information.

(c)   To assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk.

** 5\. THIRD PARTY LINKS**

5.1 You mind find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the content or policies of third party websites whatsoever. 

** 6\. CONTACTING US**

6.1 We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy.  Please do not hesitate to [ contact us](http://www.jobvine.co.za/Contact).
